Get ready for the time of your life!
Killer High is a horror, comedy, tv movie film directed by Jem Garrard.
Sabrina's perfectly planned high school reunion goes south
when a monster keeps killing all the guests.
Sabrina, played by Kacey Rohl.
Rosario, played by Humberly González.
Margo, played by Asha Bromfield.
Ronnie, played by Varun Saranga.
Meg, played by Nikki Duval.
George, played by Jonathan Langdon.
The Killer is a 2024 American action thriller film directed by John Woo.
It is a remake of Woo's 1989 film.
The film stars Nathalie Emmanuel, Omar Sy, Sam Worthington,
Diana Silvers, Eric Cantona, and Saïd Taghmaoui.
It was released in the United States by the streaming
service Peacock on August 23, 2024.
The film explores themes of high school, mascot, reunion, warthog, rampage.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.